square1art.com 2017-12-12

# Privacy Policy | Square 1 Art

###  Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Last updated: November 28, 2016

At Square 1 Art, we are committed to protecting every User’s privacy. We use the information we collect to process orders and to provide a more personalized service. Square 1 Art’s privacy policy, set forth below, is designed to use the information we collect about visitors with the utmost care and responsibility.

  1. Information Collected

We collect personal information when you register with Square 1 Art, LLC, when you use any of our products or services. Personal information is any information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address or phone number, Facebook Connect sign-in information (if applicable), and any other information that is not otherwise publicly available. If you order products or pay for services, we will need your shipping address, billing name and address, as well as the credit card number and expiration date.

You may access and use the Site solely for your personal, noncommercial use. Except as expressly authorized hereunder, the Site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, reverse-engineered or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without Square 1 Art, LLC’s prior written authorization. We reserve the right to alter or discontinue the Site, in whole or in part, at any time in Square 1 Art, LLC’s sole discretion.

  2. Artwork Submission

Persons under 18 may NOT submit any artwork for publication. Only Parents and Coordinators are allowed to submit the artwork of those under 18.

  3. Use of Information

We use your personal information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for products and services, administrative purposes, to improve our services, to customize the advertising and content you see, to contact you, and for internal business purposes. We use third party personal information you provide to us solely to provide services you specifically request.

For example, sharing your artwork/pictures electronically through Square 1 Art, LLC’s share service is one of the key benefits we offer. Square 1 Art, LLC’s share service includes both Square 1 Art, LLC’s general share service, which allows you to send others a one-time email to view artwork as well as our service that allows you to create a special website and invite recipients to participate in that website (collectively, the “Share Service”). Our Share Service allows you to send an email invitation to your selected recipients, and then to allow access artwork to view, save, or purchase products from your artwork. This invitation email would contain a web link directing that recipient to create their own account in order to view, save or purchase products from your artwork. The email also may include information about special promotional offers from Square 1 Art, LLC and/or carefully-screened third parties.

Please be assured that we do not use the email addresses that you enter through our Share Service of any of our website to send any type of direct marketing to your friends and family. (Of course, if a friend or family member signs up with Square 1 Art, LLC or any of our family of companies or we receive their email address from another unrelated source, we may communicate with them in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We use anonymous information, such as that pertaining to web pages you’ve viewed, in order to analyze trends, track user’s movements, provide a better website experience and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not use this data in a manner that would identify you personally.

  4. Information Sharing With Third Parties

Square 1 Art, LLC does not share the personal information we collect with any companies who work with or on behalf of Square 1 Art, LLC.

Every now and then, Square 1 Art, LLC will invite customers to take part in surveys, promotions, contests and sweepstakes. The information we collect from these surveys, promotions, contests and sweepstakes may be matched with individual customer accounts and used by Square 1 Art, LLC to improve your overall customer experience, and may be shared with select third parties.

Like almost all e-commerce websites, we use cookies. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

Our cookies don’t store any of your personal information. When authorized by us, Square 1 Art, LLC does share certain anonymous information with third parties (specifically Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting), such as that pertaining to web pages you’ve viewed and tracking cookies (including Google advertising cookies and other anonymous identifiers), in order to report website traffic, analyze trends, track user’s movements, provide a better website experience and gather demographic information for aggregate use. We use this information to compile anonymous statistics about our visitors in order to improve our services and our product focus. We do not share information which would identify you personally and we do not facilitate any merging of personally identifiable data with the non-personally identifiable data collected. You may opt out anonymous information sharing with Google Analytics here: [Opt-Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

  5. Opting Out Of Information Sharing

We understand and respect that not all customers may want to allow us to share any information with other select companies. If you do not want Square 1 Art to share your customer information, please immediately email us at [info@square1art.com](mailto:info@square1art.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Inquiry). When contacting us, please clearly state your request, including your name, mailing address, email address and phone number.

You may opt out of anonymous information sharing with Google Analytics here: [Opt-out](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2700409).

However, under the following circumstances, we may still be required to share your personal information:

  * If we respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or if we need to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * If we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Square 1 Art, LLC Terms of Use or as otherwise required by law.
  * Restrict or inhibit any other user from using the Site, including, without limitation, by means of “hacking” or defacing any portion of the Site;

  6. Children’s Information

We do not target our website to children. We do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. If you are a parent, guardian, or other person and become aware of information collected from an individual under 13, please contact us immediately at 888-332-3294.

  7. Access to Your Account Information and Preferences

You have the right and ability to edit your member account information, which is accessible in the My Account section of the website.

You can opt in or out of receiving future communications of special offers and new product information, or you can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages you receive. We do reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the services Square 1 Art, LLC, provide, such as service announcements and administrative messages, which are considered part of your account membership. We do not offer you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving those messages.

  8. Confidentiality and Security

We have implemented a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and/or disclosure.

We use a secure socket server (SSL) to encrypt all of your personal information during the checkout phase of the ordering process. We also have other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with industry best practices and federal regulations to protect the security and confidentiality of the personal information we have collected, and to prevent unauthorized access to or disclosure of any of your personal information.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your Information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information provided on, to, or through our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not liable for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on this Website.

  9. Third Party Site

Our website may contain links to other website for news and other information. Our Privacy Policy only applies to all of the website of the Square 1 Art, LLC. Practices or the content of other website which are linked to or integrated with the website of the Square 1 Art, LLC family. You should check the privacy policies of those Site before providing your personal information to them. See our Terms and Conditions for additional information.

  10. Your Consent

By providing information on, to, or through this Website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to this Privacy Policy and other applicable terms, then do not continue to use this Website.

  11. Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update our users accordingly. Such update will be indicated by posting those changes on this page, and may be indicated through an email notification. The date this Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for periodically visiting our Website and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

  12. Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at [info@square1art.com](mailto:info@square1art.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Inquiry) or 888-332-3294.
